《越狱》前情回顾
previously on prison break
我们要去哪
So where to, man.
想去哪就去哪
anywhere we want.
我不是你认识的哥哥了
I'm not the brother you remember.
我已经变了
I've changed.
我要做一件
And I am gonna do something
很多人都觉得恐怖的事情
that a lot of people are gonna think is horrible.
你只要记住和你一起长大的哥哥
And you just remember the brother you grew up with.
她不在这里
She's not here.
- 喂? - 莎拉
- yeah? - sara,
船要开了
The ship is leaving.
我已经上船了
I'm already on board.
我爱你
Love you.
为什么现在对我说这些?
Why are you telling me this now?
如果能再给我一次机会
If I had to it all over again,
我会重新开始
I'd do it different, you know?
锁骨和轴转肌位置
Collar bone and rotator cuff.
如果再往右6英寸  你就挂了
Six inches to the right, you're dead.
你都已经走到这一步了
You've come so far.
- 我还要走多远? - 你很幸运
How much further would I have to go?  -Well, you're lucky.
因为你只需要去趟巴拿马
For this you only have to go to panama.
- 那人找到他了 - 在哪?
- he found him.- Where?
刚刚登上去巴拿马的飞机
He just boarded a plane to panama city.
他妈的去巴拿马干什么?
What the hell's he doing in panama?
愿意戴假发吗?
You like wigs?
只要你有钱
For the right money,
我什么都愿意
I like anything.
网上有什么留言?
What about the message board?
那个金翅雀网?
The goldfinch thing?
有一条苏克雷的
There is a message from sucre.
还在跑路?
Still running, huh?
"钱还在帝博格那儿"
Says the bag still has the bag.
"他在巴拿马城的芬黛卡米诺酒店"
"He's in panama city at the fin del camino hotel.
"如果你在那"
"If you're there "
"想把钱拿回来的话"
and want to help put that bird back in the cage,
"跟我说一声 苏克雷"
let me know.sucre
等会见
see you soon!
迈克尔
Michael!
Michael
斯科菲尔德...
Scofield...
和广告里的一样帅
one thing's for sure, you're just as pretty as advertised.
是更帅
Prettier, even.
帮帮我 求你了
You got to help me, please.
不
No!
你再说一句话 就割了你喉咙
You say a word, I'm gonna cut your throat out!
斯科菲尔德
scofield!
喂?
- hello?
帕姆 是我
- Pam, it's me.
- 卡姆在睡觉 - 是吗?
Cam's napping.-Yeah?
他怎么样?
How's he doing?
很好 今天是他第一天回学校
Good, it was his first day back at school.
那就好
That's great.
你现在在哪?
Where are you?
我在国外
Um, I'm, uh, out of the country.
一切都还好吗?
Is everything all right?
还记得我常说那一天会来的
Remember how I always said that the day would come
我会歇下来?
and I'd be done?
离开联邦调查局 再不回头?
Leave the bureau and never look back?
当然
Yes.
就是今天
Today's that day.
我还有一件事情要处理
I have one more thing to do,
等我做完
and once I do it,
一切都会重归旧位
everything is going to fall into place.
而我也会休息
And I, I'll be done.
我希望你是认真的
I hope you mean it.
帕姆 如果... 如果我不再做这个工作
Pam, if-if, if I didn't have this job hanging over me anymore,
如果我是自由身...
if I were free, if I were free...
阿历克斯...
alex...
我想知道
I need to know.
我不会拒绝你的
I'm not saying no.
我发誓 我会重新回来
I will make this right, I swear to god.
你 我 还有卡姆...
And you and me and cam...
我要挂了
I-I have to go.
我会一直爱你 帕姆 永远爱你
I never stopped loving you, pam, ever.
万事小心 阿历克斯
Just be safe, alex.
- 准备好了吗? - 是
You in position?-yeah.
10分钟后到
I'll be there in ten minutes.
收到
Got it.
这样行吗?
es bueno?(西班牙语)
很好
Es bueno.
谢谢你
Gracias.
这个能给我吗?
Necesitas los otros?
送给你了
Son tuyos.
谢谢
Gracias.
不用谢
De nada.
迈克尔...
Michael...
怎么了?
what's wrong?
又见面了 斯科菲尔德?
Que paso, scofield?
跟我来
Come on.
我喜欢这样
I love iT.
你来这也为了抢那500万
Mr.Above it all down here trying to sniff out that $5 million
跟我们这些小混混一样
just like the rest of us riff-raff.
你跟我没什么两样 斯科菲尔德
See?You ain't no better than me, scofield.
我来这只是为了抓帝博格
I want t-bag locked up.It's the only reason I'm here.
想当骑警杜德雷吗?
Aw, dudley freakin' do-right, huh?
没想到你会来这里 迈克尔
I didn't know you were gonna be here, michael.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
是你在网上发消息给我 说帝博格在这里
You e-mailed me.You said t-bag was here.It's on the web site.
什么?  不可能
What?No.
我没在网上发消息给任何人  包括你在内
I didn't write anything on the web site to you or anybody else.
帝博格在那家酒店里吗?
Is t-bag in that hotel?
对 两个警察守在街对面
Yeah, a couple feds staking it out across the street.
那你帮我们把500万拿过来
Well, then you're gonna help us get it then.
你没看到有警察吗
Maybe you missed the part about the feds.
我不管 我长途跋涉来到 这种鸟不拉屎的地方
I don't care.I didn't travel 2,000 miles down the diarrhea trail to get to this backward-ass country
可不会就这么空手而归的
to not get my $5 million!
那就太糟糕了
Well, that's too bad
因为这里越看越象个局
'cause this is looking more and more like a setup.
那就用你大学生的脑子好好想想办法
Well, then get that little college boy brain of yours to work then.
如果你觉得我只是说着玩的
And if you don't think I'm serious,
那就尽管把你的狱友们叫来 看看我会怎么做
just ask your old cellie here what length I'll go to.
玛丽克鲁兹被他囚禁在某个地方
He's got maricruz locked away somewhere.
你一定要帮他拿到钱
You're gonna help him get the money
否则她就死定了
or she's dead.
没错
Yeah,
我是个大混蛋 斯科菲尔德
I'm a big jerk, scofield.
我就是可耻
Shame on me.
迈克尔 我根本没资格要求你什么
Michael, I'm, I'm in no position to ask you for anything.
但我需要你的帮忙 兄弟 真的
I need your help, papi, I do.
想加入吗
Are you in
还是...?
or what?
把枪拿开
get the gun off me.
我问你话呢
I asked you a question.
叫你把枪拿开 否则我就走了
I said get the gun off me or I walk.
好吧 500万是你的了
All right, you get your $5 million.
你找到你的玛丽克鲁兹
You get maricruz,
我抓到我的帝博格
and I get t-bag.
三赢嘛
Win, win, win.
但是你要照我说的做
But you got to do exactly what I say.
谢谢你 兄弟
Thank you, bro.
好吧   "爱因斯坦" 你想怎么做?
All right, einstein, what you thinking?
今天已经是对莎拉 唐克雷蒂 庭审的第三天
And it's the third day of testimony in the trial of dr.Sara tancredi,
也就是上一届州长富兰克 唐克雷蒂的女儿
daughter of the late governor frank tancredi.
目前为止 专家们认为起诉过程进展顺利
So far, pundits feel the prosecution is well on its way
控方将会提供证据
to meeting its burden of proof
以证明她各项罪名成立
and getting a conviction on all counts.
辩方律师  请开始
Defense counsel, you may proceed.
法官大人 我请求播放编号为 "辩方证物D"的带子
Your honor, at this time I ask this tape be marked "defense exhibit 'D.
反对 大人 这盘带子根本就是
'" Objection.Your honor, this tape is the very propaganda
迈克尔 斯科菲尔德和林肯 布伦斯对外使用的宣传片
that michael scofield and lincoln burrows released to the media
其真实性已受到质疑
that was summarily debunked.
陪审团依旧有权再看一遍
The jury still has a right to hear it.
里面的内容都是道听途说
The tape is hearsay.
证人难以出席的情况下可以例外 大人
Unavailable witness exception, your honor.
证人难以出席
The witness is only unavailable
就因为他本身也是个逃犯
because he's a fugitive on the run.
即便如此
Be that as it may,
他在带子上所说的话
his statement on this tape
可以证明唐克雷蒂无罪
exonerates dr.Tancredi.
大人...
Your honor...
允许播放
the tape is allowed.
反对意见会被记录在案
The state's objection will be noted in the record.
很多的责任都被归结于另一无辜者身上
Much blame has been placed on another innocent person--
莎拉 唐克雷蒂医生
dr.Sara tancredi.
他与我们越狱无关
She had nothing to do with our escape.
莎拉 如果你在听...   我知道
Sara, if you're listening,
我不能再要求你给我个机会
I know I can't ask you for another chance,
我只希望你已到了一个安全的港湾
I only hope by now you've found your safe haven.
对于前州长唐克雷蒂之女
The trial of the late governor tancredi's daughter,
莎拉 唐克雷蒂医生的审判今天在库克郡继续进行
dr.Sara tancredi continues today in cook county.
唐克雷蒂医生的执照已被暂停
Dr.Tancredi, whose medical license has been suspended
审判结果还未出来
pending the outcome of the trial,
她面临多项指控 包括协助...
is facing multiple counts ranging from aiding...
我要杀了那该死的
I'm gonna kill him.
之后再回到监狱?
And go right back to prison.
我不管 等我们拿到钱
I don't care.Once we get the money
等他告诉我玛丽克鲁兹在哪 我就宰了他
and he tells me where maricruz is, I'm gonna kill him.
如果你找到了玛丽克鲁兹 你要和她结婚
If you find maricruz you're going to marry maricruz
然后去过幸福的生活
and live happily ever after.
是的 等我先给贝利克一刀子
Yeah, after I sink a knife in bellick's chest.
贝利克和帝博格会得到他们应得的 相信我
Bellick and t-bag will get theirs, trust me.
难道福克斯河没让你学到点什么吗?
Didn't fox river teach you anything, man?
外面的游戏规则其实也一样
'Cause the same rules apply out here.
有罪 无罪 这都无所谓
It doesn't make a difference if you're guilty or innocent.
得看谁活得久
It's who survives.
你不是那样的人
You're not that guy.
那狗娘养的把我女友抓走 关起来
That son of a bitch took my girl, locked her up somewhere.
我现在就是那样的人 迈克尔
I am that guy now, michael.
你自己瞧瞧
Look at me.
我在这里的唯一原因就是
The only reason I'm not five miles away from here right now is
我想帮你找到玛丽克鲁兹 不是杀贝利克
because I want to help you find maricruz, not kill bellick.
如果你非要如此
And if that's your game,
那恕我不能奉陪
I'm gone.
相信我 我理解你的那种冲动
Believe me, I understand the impulse to pull the trigger.
但如果我们不能控制好自己 那就全完了
But if we lose ourselves, we lose evything.
已经一周了
It's been a week.
我不知道她在哪
I don't know where she is.
我很怕
I'm scared.
我们会找到她的
We'll find her.
怎么回事?
What the hell's this?
大家请注意
酒店发生火警
请各位马上有序离开
大家请注意
酒店发生火警
请各位马上有序离开
听着 如果你们现在鲁莽行事的话
Now, if you start acting like a cowboy
事情立刻会变得很糟糕 记住
this whole thing's going south real fast, remember that.
走
Here we go.
你不希望如此结束的 林肯
you're not going to like how this ends, lincoln.
我现在给你机会
I'm giving you a chance.
就现在
Right now.
你... 退后  行么?
Just...back away, all right?
退后
Just back away.
你个狗娘养的 是你杀了我父亲?
The son of a bitch, you killed my dad?
你完了
You're done.
上次挨了子弹的伤还没好把 马宏?
those bullet holes don't heal too good, do they, mahone?
把手铐给我
Toss me the handcuffs.
把手铐给我 否则我发誓
Hand 'em over or I swear to god
我会一枪轰了你脑袋的
I'll blow your head clean off.
是美国人吧?
Americans?
是的
Yeah.
哦 谢天谢地
Oh, thank, god.
你们知道瓜得鲁普大教堂在哪么?
Do you know where the cathedral guadalupe is?
没听说过
Never heard of it.
半小时前我和我老伴说好在那见面的
I was supposed to meet my old lady there a half hour ago.
那很好啊
That's great.
他们都说一定找的到的 可我就是找不到
They say you can't miss it, but I missed it.
我在想你们是不是带了
I was wondering you had
旅行手册什么的在身边?
maybe a travel guide or something on you?
你为何不接着走呢 老兄?
Why don't you just keep on walking, pal?
我以为我能在美国老乡那得到点帮助呢
Well, excuse me for thinking I could ask for a little help from some fellow americans.
听着 给我走开
Listen, beat it.
喂 伙计们
Hello, boys.
过的还好吧 伙计们?
So how we doing,gentmen.
苏克雷 把枪给我
Sucre, the gun.
快点
Come on.
进那巷子里去
Get in the alley.
这是一个全球性的问题
it is a global problem.
48% 北美的湖泊富营养化
48% of north american lakes are eutrophic.
在欧洲有53%...
It's 53% in europe...
－克里斯丁 －什么事?
- kristine.- Yeah?
是你哥哥 保罗
It's your brother, paul.
什么 怎么了?
What, what's going on?
你好
hello.
他就在这幢房子里
He's in this building right here.
我们得行动了
We got to move.
让我看下你们的证件
Let's see your i.D.
联邦调查局的?
Feds?
不 如果是的话  他们就会跟着帝博格了
No, if these guys were, they'd be after t-bag.
是公司派来的?
You guys company?
快点 苏克雷
Come on, sucre,
把他们绑起来
let's wrap these numb nuts up.
你们在这做什么? 你们想干吗?
what are you guys doing here?What do you want?
我不喜欢这样  有些不对劲
I don't like this.Something's up.
快点  苏克雷  动作快点
Come on, sucre, let's move it.
我们走  快
Now, let's go, come on.
走吧 迈克尔
Let's go, michael.
我们知道你在这儿  巴戈威尔
We know you're in here, bagwell!
我数到三
Three to one
开始啦
...do the math.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay,
我可不想惹什么麻烦
don't want any trouble.
把枪扔过来
Slide the gun over.
总有办法解决的  伙计们
We can work something out, boy.
把枪扔过来
Slide the gun over.
钱在哪儿
Where's the money?
谁叫的警察
who called the cops?
你有三秒钟回答
You got three seconds,hillbilly.
一…
One...
就在那儿
in there.
去拿过来
Get it.
谁想要谁去拿
You want it, you get it.
我们没有时间了  贝利克
We don't have time for this, bellick.
现在不是做傻事的时候
Nothing stupid now.
这可不是在玩游戏
You're not playing a game.
把门打开
Open it.
苏克雷  过去看看!
Sucre, move your ass!
迈克尔
Michael!
这是个圈套
it's a trap.
给我停下来  帝博格
freeze, bagwell!
快去把钱拿回来
get the money!
你要是想和那个女孩儿一起   就快去把钱拿回来
You want the girl,get the money!
别动
Don'T.
不准动
有话好好说
we can work something out.
走
Move.
－我是无辜的  －苏克雷 我们走
-Innocente!-Sucre, we got to go.
那个帝博格  他才是你们要抓的人
bagwell--he's the one
他杀的那个妓女
you want for that dead chick in there.
有谁会说英语的
anybody speak english?
我什么都没做
I didn't do it!
我向上帝发誓  我什么都没有做
I swear to god I didn't do it!
不要  求你们了  求你们了
No, please, please!
我们就在这里把钱分了吧  然后我们各走各路
We can do a little divvying right here,then we'll go our separate ways.
苏克雷  去帮我们弄辆车
Sucre, I want you to get us a car.
什…什么?  你又有什么计划
Wh-what's going on?What's the plan?
我说  给我们弄辆车来
I said, get us a car.
看来你最近交了些朋友
Looks like you've made some friends lately.
我不懂你说什么
I don't follow.
刚才那个小把戏
That little set-up back there--
可不像你的惯用手法
just a little out of your league.
看上去还挺像真的
Looked almost professional.
让我们来谈谈
Let's say that's the case.
你发现了这些又有什么用呢
What's it worth to you to find out?
不过我掌握了一些情报
Because i am in possession of some information
你也许会需要  帅哥
that you might need, pretty.
好吧  告诉我你知道些什么
Okay. Tell me what you know.
也许我会放你走...
Maybe I'll let you walk...
钱得留下
without the money.
真的?
Yeah?
是
Yeah.
你会放我走?
You're gonna let me traipse on out of here?
得看你知道什么
Depends on the information.
谁指使你的?
Who's pulling your strings?
你知道么  我有个直觉
You know, I got a hunch
我觉得你在说谎  帅哥
you're speaking with a forked tongue, pretty.
要我说  我们到公共场所去
So I'm gonna tell you what, we go someplace public
找辆可以让我离开的车  那时
with a car waiting for me to leave, and then...
到那时我再告诉你  怎么样?
then I'll tell you. Deal?
不行
No.
哦 天哪
oh, my god.
保罗
Paul.
这只是第二次...
that is only the second time...
我的枪居然卡住了
a weapon has ever jammed on me.
第一次是在海湾战争的训练中
First time was during training for gulf one.
这事一发生 我的长官
As soon as it happened,the commanding officer,
走过来 对我说
he got in my face and he said,
"孩子 要是在战场上如此
"son, a weapon jam on the battlefield,
这跟自杀没什么两样"
you might as well call that suicide."
克里斯丁 我...
kristine, I've, uh...
做的那些事情...
done things...
该死
damn.
我爱你  保罗 不管你做了什么
I love you, paul, whatever it is that got you here.
都会有办法解决的  相信我
And there's a way out,believe me.
我...
My...
我长大成人后...
entire... my entire adult life,
我听从命令...
I've followed orders...
做了很多骇人的事
uh, and I did terrible things,
因为我觉得这些都是好事...
because I thought they were right, and...
但结果我的所作所为毫无意义
it turns out I did those things in service of nothing.
所以我要一无所有地离开
So that's what I'm left with-- nothing.
你还有我
you have me.
对  还有你
Yeah, okay.
你还有清白的一生
And you have a clean slate.
任何事情...
Anything.
所有事情...
Everything.
你都可以重新开始
It's available to you starting right now.
- 事情已经发生了  克里斯丁...  - 那就解释清楚
The things I've done,kristine...-undo them.
保罗
Paul
总会有解决的办法的
there's always a way.
也许枪坏掉就是有原因的
Maybe that gun jammed for a reason.
来
Come here.
不要高兴得太早了  帅哥
don'T...let your pride get in the way now, pretty.
省省吧
Save it.
把我送回监狱对你的处境没什么帮助
Locking me up ain't gonna help your situation none.
我有你要的信息
I have information.
你想怎么做?
what's the plan?
送他去大使馆
We're gonna take him to the embassy,
确保他被驱逐出境
we're gonna make sure he's deported,
然后再去找贝利克  行不行?
then we'll go looking for bellick, all right?
- 行 - 我要你跟他一起坐后面
-Si.-Meanwhe,I want you to ride in the back with him.
我奉劝你  不要到头来 捡了芝麻 丢了西瓜
I'm telling you, you are being penny-wise and pound-foolish.
上车
Get in the car.
我告诉她这提案
I'll tell her about the offer.
怎么样?
Well?
12年
12 years.
不可能
No.
不可能  陪审团看了迈克尔的带子
No. The jury heard michael's tape.
他们看到的是一个重罪犯 为他心爱的女人撒谎
They heard a convicted felon lie for a woman that he clearly cares for.
他没什么可性度
He's got no credibility.
莎拉  我们必须正视他们的提案
Sara, we need to take a hard look at what they're offering.
恕我不敬 马蒂 你是没关系 入狱的是我
Due respect, marty, we aren't going to prison, i am.
他们已说的很清楚了
They've made it very clear that
他们肯定要找个替死鬼
they want somebody to hang for this,
莎拉 不幸的是  你是现在
sara,and unfortunately,you're the only one
唯一被抓在他们手里的人
they've got in their grasp.
这是无可避免的
There's no avoiding it.
这是协议书
This is the plea agreement.
如果你同意的话 我们可帮你办妥
We can walk you through it if you'd like.
12年？
12 years?
他没回复
he didn't answer.
希望你弟弟能够顺利回到船上
I certainly hope your brother makes it back to that boat.
要是他没有呢？
And if he doesn't?
你还是看看你自己吧
You should see yourself.
你自己也命悬一线了
You look like you're hanging in there by a thread.
我只是想赶快结束
I just want this over with.
那你就根本不该来这儿
Then you should never have come down here.
也许你还没不知道
In case you hadn't noticed,
我弟弟和我做任何事都是有原因的
me and my brother don't quit for no one.
感谢上帝
Thank god for that.
正因为有你们这样的犯人
Because it's guys that are accused of things like
才让我这样的人有事可做
you are that guys like me in business.
或者说
Kept...
一直以来 让我有事可做
guys like me in business, rather.
伙计 结局对你可不怎么好
It's gonna end bad for you, man.
这世界上有几件事是我非常擅长的
Couple of things in this world I'm good at.
其中一件就是看着一个人的眼睛
One of them's looking into a man's eye
我就知道他什么时候会被打败
and knowing when he's beat.
大使馆还有多远
How far to the embassy?
老兄 安安稳稳坐那吧
Just hang in there, buddy.
然后呢？
And then what?
- 把他送进大牢 - 那我们怎样才能不被逮到
We're gonna turn 'em in.-And how do we not get busted?
到那儿之前 我会先停车
Before we get there,I'll pull over.
用胶带把他绑起来
We'll hog-tie him with duct tape,
扔出去  丢在路上
and we'll dump him out,and hit the road,
然后打电话给警察  告诉他们地点
and I'll call the cops,tell 'em where we left him.
那我们怎么找到贝利克呢？
Then how do we get bellick?
别担心  会找到他
Don't worry,we'll find him.
- 你们已经离贝利克一英里远了 - 没人问你
Y'all ain't getting within a mile of bellick.-Nobody asked you.
不过他说得也对  迈克尔
He's got a point,though, michael.
只管拿枪对着他  行吗
Just keep the gun on him, okay?
我的意思是
I mean,
如果贝利克被抓了
if bellick's locked up,
我们拿到钱又有什么用
what's good the money going to be to us?
老兄  我说了我们能搞定的
Buddy, I told you we'll fix it.
我女朋友危在旦夕
My girl's life is on the line here.
苏克雷  我们必须齐心协力
Sucre, you better pull it together.
叫救护车
ambulancia!
快叫救护车!
Ambulaia!
放松  放松
Easy. Easy.
伙计 你会没事的
Buddy, you're gonna be all right.
去拿钱
go get the money.
求你了  快
Please. Quick.
过来 快过来
Venga!  Venga!
来了 来了
Bueno. Bueno, bueno.
去拿钱
Get the money.
帮个忙...
For favor...
帮我压着
pressure. Pression.
好的
Si, si, si.
帅哥  你到底想要什么？
What exactly is it that you want, pretty?
我要把你送进监狱
I'm taking you in.
是那样吗  真的？
Is that it? Really?
不是要钱？
It ain't about the money?
如果是 你尽管告诉我
'Cause, if it is,you can tell me.
这没别人 就我们两个
Ain't nobody here but us cons.
你是想走出去 还是被拖出去
You can walk or get dragged.
自己选吧
But it's up to you.
你错了 刚才你拿枪指着我时
No. See, when you had the gun on me,
我只能听你的
I afforded you a certain respect.
但现在?
But here?
天平已经向我这边倾斜了
Well, the scales are tipped back my way.
所以现在的选项应该由我来定
So I'm going to spell out the present options.
要么我们平分
Either we split this money,
你可以去多做些纹身
and you can go get your legs tattooed
想干什么都行
or whatever the hell it is you want,
要么就等着别人发现你的尸体
or they're going to find your corpse
在那凳子上膨胀腐烂
slumped over that there chair
裤子都掉到脚上
with your pants down around your ankles,
因为这里很少有人来的 靓仔
'cause it's been a long time coming, pretty.
看来我知道答案了
Well, I got my answer.
废话说完了就动手吧
Whener you're done yakking.
来吧 狗娘养的
Bring it, bitch.
你骗谁啊?
who are you fooling?
你不会杀我的 亲爱的迈克尔先生
You ain't going to kill me,Michel angelo.
你下不了手 干吗不让我来替你
You ain't got it in you,so why don't you let me
动手呢?
do the killing?
好的
all right.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了 莎拉
Okay, sara.
现在听我说 程序是这样的
Now, here's how the plea is going to go down.
法官需要你当庭认罪
The judge is going to need you to allocute to the charges.
他会问你
He's going to ask you
是不是故意没有锁门
if you intentionally left the door open.
你要回答是的
You will say yes.
是
Right.
然后他会接着问你
Then he's going to ask you
你是不是在迈克尔和林肯越狱后
if you gave support and comfort
给他们提供过支持和帮助
to michael scofield and lincoln burrows since the escape.
你要回答是的
You'll say yes.
然后就会立即宣判
And the sentence will be immediately handed down.
检控官会要求
The prosecution is asking that
把你安排在防卫设施最严密的地方服刑
you do your time in a maximum security facility.
我想法官会批准的
I think the judge is going to agree to that.
好的 呃...
Okay. Um...
如果好好表现的话
with good behavior,
在被判12年的情况下
how many years of my sentence can I expect to serve?
我最少要服刑多少年?
On a 12 year sentence?
9年
You'll do nine years.
那我40岁之前可以出来了
I'll be out before I'm 40.
我很抱歉 莎拉
I'm sorry, sara.
莎拉?
Sara?
你准备好了吗?
Are you ready for this?
什么?
What?
刚刚来了位可信度极高的证人
A very credible witness has just came forward,
他愿意出庭作证
and he's willing to testify.
你所有关于这项阴谋的供词
He'll corroborate everything
他都愿意帮你作证
you've said about this conspiracy.
是谁?
Who?
各单位注意
Attention all units
我重复下受害者提供的消息
I repeat the victim saw
袭击者跑向了东北方向
his assailant run northeast.
跑进了林子 大约3号高速公路36英里处
into the forest at approximately mile 36 of highway 3
救命
Help!
林肯
linc!
你好
Hola.
...您...讲英语吗?
Uh... do you...do you speak english?
好的 好的 我要...
Good. Good. I need to, uh...
我想接通巴拿马城内
I need to get in contact
每家医院的电话
with every hospital in the panama city area.
我有个朋友 呃...
A friend of mine was, uh...
我有个朋友出了车祸
a friend of mine was in a car accident.
抱歉  我一会再打过来
I'm sorry. I'm going to have to call you back.
林肯?
Linc?
对不起  兄弟
I'm sorry, man.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
你好  迈克尔
Hello, michael.
如果敢碰我哥哥  你就死定了
If you touch my brother,you're a dead man.
不要那样
Oh, please.
这你不必担心
You don't have to worry about that.
但是  说到这个
But, when it comes right down to it,
他像你一样
he's just like you.
善良  绝不会去杀人
He has a heart that won't kill a man.
把手铐给我
Give me the handcuffs
否则  我让你脑袋开花
or, I swear to god,I'll blow your head clean off.
你想怎样  阿历克斯?
what do you want, alex?
我会告诉你的
I'll tell you exactly what I want.
但是首先
But first things first.
今天当帝博格被捕时
When the authorities captured bagwell today,
钱已经不见了
the money was nowhere to be found.
我想应该是你拿到了钱
Now, i can only assume that you've got the money...
现在又上了克里斯蒂娜 罗丝号
aboard the christina rose right noW.
真是个惊人的计划  迈克尔
It's an amazing plan, michael.
拿到钱  登上船  永远地消失
Take the money, take the boat,disappear forever.
但是你...
But you...
不是唯一想要消失的人
are not the only one that needs to disappear
你还在听吗?
You still there?
是的  我在听
Yeah, I'm still here.
很好  我要你听好我所说的话
Good. Because I'm going to say this,
我只说一遍
and I'm going to say this once.
把钱给我  把船给我
Bring me the money,bring me the boat.
你疯了
You are out of your mind.
没有
Not really.
我们都有对方需要的东西
We both have something the other person needs.
归根结底  迈克尔
It all comes down to this,michael.
这计划都是为了你哥哥
Your brother for your plan.
我只给你五分钟时间
Five minutes.That's what you have.